[
  {
    "front": "수의사",
    "back": "Vet"
  },
  {
    "front": "짖다",
    "back": "Bark"
  },
  {
    "front": "신이 난",
    "back": "Thrilled"
  },
  {
    "front": "꺼내다",
    "back": "Pull out"
  },
  {
    "front": "다시",
    "back": "Again"
  },
  {
    "front": "엄마",
    "back": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "front": "아기",
    "back": "Baby"
  },
  {
    "front": "말하다",
    "back": "Say"
  },
  {
    "front": "말",
    "back": "Horse"
  },
  {
    "front": "고양이",
    "back": "Cat"
  }
]